https://peltiertech.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to primary navigation Skip to main content Skip to primary sidebarPeltier Tech Consulting
Thursday, August 3, 2017
by Jon Peltier Peltier Technical Services, Inc., Copyright © 2020, All rights reserved.
Privacy
I respect your privacy and I am committed to safeguarding your privacy while online at peltiertech.com. The following discloses how I gather and disseminate information for this Blog.
RSS Feeds and Email Updates
If a user wishes to subscribe to my RSS Feeds or Email Updates, I ask for contact information such as name and email address. Users may opt-out of these communications at any time. Your personal information will never be sold or given to a third party. You will never be spammed by me – ever.
Log Files and Stats
Like most blogging platforms I use Google Analytics to analyze traffic. Google stores information such as internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring, exit and visited pages, platform used, date/time stamp, track user’s movement in the whole, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. I have no access to personally identifiable information.
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. This blog doesn’t use cookies. However, some of my business partners use cookies on this site (for example – advertisers). I can’t access or control these cookies once the advertisers have set them.
Links
This Blog contains links to other sites. Please be aware that I am not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites. I advise my users to be aware of this when they leave this blog and to read the privacy statements of each and every site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this blog.
Advertisers
I use third-party advertising companies, including Google and Amazon, to serve ads when you visit this website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These advertisers may use cookies which are collected by the advertising companies; I do not have access to this information. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please check the advertisers websites for respective privacy policies.
Most advertising links on these pages are paid, either on a per-pageview basis to be hosted on this web site, or on a per-purchase basis for affiliate sales links. The commissions are not large, and I would not host ads for these affiliate products and books if I didn’t believe they were good products and worth the price.
Contact Information
If you have any questions or concerns please contact me at jon@peltiertech.com. This privacy policy was updated August 2017.
Share this:Click to share on Twitter (Opens in new window)Click to share on Facebook (Opens in new window)Click to share on LinkedIn (Opens in new window)Click to share on Tumblr (Opens in new window)Click to share on Pinterest (Opens in new window)Click to print (Opens in new window)Click to email this to a friend (Opens in new window)Click to share on Reddit (Opens in new window)Posted: Thursday, August 3rd, 2017 under .Tags: .
Comments: none
Primary SidebarPeltier Tech Blog
About Peltier Tech
About Jon Peltier
Peltier Tech Consulting
Peltier Tech Software
Peltier Tech Excel Training
Copyright and Licensing
